galvestondailynews.com 2012-05-06

# The Daily News - Serving Galveston County since 1842

Privacy Policy for The Daily News

Galveston Newspapers Inc., publisher of The Galveston County Daily News and The Daily News Web Edition, is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using our web site and related online services. 

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit or subscribe to the site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any personal information received by Galveston Newspapers Inc. in connection with your subscriptions to the print edition of The Daily News.

We may make content or services from other Web sites partnered with The Daily News available to you from links located on The Daily News Web Edition. These other sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such site to determine how that site protects your privacy.

**Information we collect**

General: When you register, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your computers, profession, investing habits and similar information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

Web Site Usage Information: We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit the site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our sites, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each page, and the length of their visits.

**How we use information collected**

We may use information in the following ways:

• For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions or registrations.

• To send you notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.

• To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.

• To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns.

• To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

We may combine the information that we collect from you on the site with information that you provide to us in connection with your use of our other products, services and sites.

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of Galveston Newspapers Inc. unless you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us.

**Compliance with legal process**

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web sites; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Subscriber Agreement or Terms of Use (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights).

**Online advertising**

When you view an ad, our third-party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The information collected is not personally identifiable and is used only to track response to our advertising efforts.

**NewsRight News Registry**

This site uses services provided by the [**NewsRight News Registry**](http://www.newsregistry.com/privacycenter/servicepolicy.aspx). The NewsRight News Registry collects content usage information and may use cookies in conjunction with this activity. Continued readership of The Daily News site means you accept the privacy policy of the NewsRight News Registry. Please refer to the [**NewsRight News Registry privacy policy**](http://www.newsregistry.com/privacycenter/servicepolicy.aspx) for further information.

**Comments and questions**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [webmaster@galvnews.com](mailto:webmaster@galvnews.com).

_Last Updated: January 13, 2012_
